that they will be able to get gas, they will not be able to take small notes
except small notes, people could not take 100 MB, fortunately in the
last 500 Modi shame on you, it is a
place of shame,
like the ICICI Bank
branch located at Jail Chauraha, customers are being harassed with new rules everyday,
people with money
cannot be turned away saying that they had
₹100 notes, then I said that I did
not have space to keep it, what are
you saying, now we do
not have the system, we will not keep it, let me
tell you that in Jhansi, the cashier of Uttar Pradesh
Transport Department had come to
deposit cash in ICICI Bank branch located at Jail Chauraha,
but the bank manager
refused saying that small notes cannot be deposited, the
transport department employee says
that he came from ten kilometers away with lakhs of rupees in cash,
but the bank manager
refused to deposit small notes, this is his argument,
after waiting for several hours, when jewelers
intervened in the matter, only then the
cash was deposited. The sharer says that he
had lakhs of rupees in cash, if some
incident had happened during this time, who would have been responsible
[music]
so that notifications of incidents could be made immediately  I am here
that I am sick since 11:00 here after 7 minutes the
media was called the players were
brought then
where are you you sit down
talk to the bank manager I saw
someone
's photo
with the security guard told me that the bank
manager always harasses him he refused to accept it saying that
if money is deposited in the bank by that
photo then
find out it you will feel
that brother it is amazing that
you say such a festival that we will do our youth
till today the machine will not be fixed
claim that Pradeep went on that how the
vision got blurred
candidate Jyoti Jyoti said that when the
bank manager talks about depositing new and small notes
then they refuse saying that this is that they
want to maintain the photo of ICICI Bank in the branch located at the highest point in the country
good C report of India Public Khabar
correspondent Brijesh Shishu
what is your opinion about this news
please tell us in the comment section so that
for all the other news of the country and the world
subscribe or Public Khabar's YouTube
channel and do not forget to press the bell icon